You might think that to lose weight you need to do strenuous exercise — like pedalling frantically on an exercise bike or swimming lengths in your local pool.
你可能会认为要减肥就需要进行剧烈的运动——比如在健身单车上拼命地蹬踏，或者在当地的游泳池里来回游泳。
But you will be delighted to learn that lying in a steaming hot bath might bring the same benefits as a workout, without all the sweat in the gym!
不过，你可能会惊喜地发现，躺在热气腾腾的浴缸里能带来与运动相同的好处，而且无需在健身房里大汗淋漓！
These were the findings of an experiment comparing the relative benefits of exercise and hot baths that was carried out by Dr Steve Faulkner of Loughborough University.
这些是拉夫堡大学的史蒂夫·福克纳博士进行的一项实验的结果，该实验比较了运动和热水浴的相对益处。
The volunteers first lay in a hot bath and then ate a light meal, while their blood sugar level was monitored and the number of calories they burnt was measured.
志愿者们先是躺在热水浴缸里，然后吃了一顿便餐，同时监测他们的血糖水平，并测量他们燃烧的卡路里数量。
The experiment was then repeated, but instead of having a bath, the participants did an hour's vigorous exercise on a bike.
然后重复这个实验，但参与者不是泡澡，而是在单车上进行了一个小时的剧烈运动。
The results from both activities were compared with unexpected results.
对这两项活动的结果进行了比较，得出了意想不到的结果。
"What we found", said Dr Faulkner, "was an 80% increase in energy expenditure, just as a result of sitting in the bath for the course of an hour".
福克纳博士说：“我们发现，因为在浴缸里坐了一个小时，能量消耗就增加了80%。”
You burn 140 calories - not as many perhaps as if you had worked out on an exercise bike, but the same number as if you had been on a brisk walk.
你燃烧了140卡路里——也许没有在健身单车上锻炼消耗的那么多，但和快走消耗的卡路里数量相同。
The real surprise, however, came in the blood sugar level results.
然而，真正令人惊讶的是血糖水平的结果。
The peak glucose output, the amount of blood sugar in the blood after a meal, was on average 10% lower after the bath compared to that after exercise.
餐后血液中的血糖量，即血糖峰值，泡澡后平均比运动后低10%。
Dr Faulkner's explanation for this phenomenon is that when you are in a hot bath, proteins, known as 'heat shock proteins' are released, which help divert the sugar from the bloodstream to the muscles.
福克纳博士对这一现象的解释是，当你泡在热水里时，被称为“热休克蛋白”的蛋白质会被释放出来，这些蛋白质有助于将糖分从血液中转移到肌肉中。
It's important to keep blood sugar levels down to avoid damage to the arteries and nerves.
保持血糖水平低很重要，以避免对动脉和神经造成损害。
Don't think, though, that you can hang up your trainers just yet!
不过，别以为你现在就可以把运动鞋收起来了！
You should aim to do at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity exercise a week.
你应该目标是每周至少进行150分钟的中等强度运动。
But, if you are one of those people who need to control their blood sugar levels - if you have type-2 diabetes for example or find it hard to exercise - why wait?
但是，如果你是那些需要控制血糖水平的人之一——比如你患有2型糖尿病，或者觉得运动很困难——那还等什么呢？
Grab a towel and start running the hot tap!
拿条毛巾，打开热水龙头吧！